Lou Blachly papers, 1827-1965
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series XIV: Oral History Recordings, 1851-1960
  - Brice, Josh - Interview Roswell, New Mexico(continued from reel 124), June 29, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 2, Reel 125)
    Jim Miller - Killing of Jaynes by unknown, Trail of Miller for subordinating Joe Erp, Killing of John Wesley Harden, John Selman and Bea Scarb, Coming to News Mexico, Trial of murder cases by Col. E.P. Bujar (continued on reel 126)
  - I: Brice, Josh - Interview Roswell, New Mexico (continued from reel 125), II: Life of Caesar Brock, chapters 1 and 2 (continued on reel 127); June 29, 1953; undated (Box 44, Folder 2, Reel 126)
  - I: Life of Caesar Brock, chapters 1 and 2 (continued from reel 126), II: Life of Caesar Brock, chapters 3, 4, and 5 (continued on reel 128); undated (Box 44, Folder 3, Reel 127)
  - I: Life of Caesar Brock, chapters 3, 4, and 5 (continued on reel 127 and on reel 129), II: Life of Caesar Brock, chapter 7 (continued on reel 129); undated (Box 44, Folder 3, Reel 128)
  - I: Life of Caesar Brock, chapter 7 (continued from reel 128), II: Life of Caesar Brock, chapters 8 and 9 (continued on reel 130); undated (Box 44, Folder 4, Reel 129)
  - I: Life of Caesar Brock, chapters 8 and 9 (continued from reel 129 and on 131), undated (Box 44, Folder 4, Reel 130)
  - I: Life of Caesar Brock, chapter 9 (continued from reel 130, II: Brock, Henry and Cox, John - Interviews (continued on reel 132); undated; April 11, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 5, Reel 131)
  - II: Brock, Henry and Cox, John - Interviews (continued from reel 131 an on 133), April 11, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 5, Reel 132)
  - I: Brock, Henry and Cox, John - Interviews (continued from reel 132 an on 134), April 11, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 6, Reel 133)
  - I: Brock, Henry and Cox, John - Interviews (continued from reel 133), II: Brock Henry - Interview; April 11, 1953; undated (Box 44, Folder 6, Reel 134)
  - II: Brock Henry - Interview (continued from reel 134), undated (Box 44, Folder 7, Reel 135)
    Recollections of Diamond A Cowboys (continued on reel 136),
  - I: Brock Henry - Interview (Box 44, Folder 7, Reel 136)
    Recollections of Diamond A Cowboys, Recollections of Bud Moore, Beginning of the Diamond A, Following of the Mormon Battalion (continued from reel 135 on 137)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview, June 11, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 8, Reel 137)
    Recollections of Bud Moore Beginning of the Diamond A, Following of the Mormon Battalion (continued from reel 136)
  - II: Brock, Henry Interview Birth and parentage (continued on reel 138), June 13, 1952 (Box 44, Folder  8, Reel 137)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview - Birth and parentage (continued from reel 137), II: Brock, Henry Interview - First days on the job with the Diamond A (continued on reel 139); June 13, 1952; June 16, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 8, Reel 138)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview - First days on the job with the Diamond A (continued from reel 138), II: Brock, Henry Interview - Overstocking (continued on 140); June 16, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 1, Reel 139)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview - Overstocking (continued from 139), II: Brock, Henry Interview - The Last Longhorn - Stampede Trail Drive (continued on reel 141); June 16, 1952; June 17, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 1, Reel 140)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview - The Last Longhorn - Stampede Trail Drive (continued on reel 140), II: Brock, Henry Interview - Later Years (continued on reel 142); June 17, 1952; undated (Box 45, Folder 2, Reel 141)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview - Later Years (continued from reel 141), undated (Box 45, Folder 2, Reel 142)
  - II: Brock, Henry Interview, April 13, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 2, Reel 142)
    Bud Moore and Indian Killings, War between bandits Cattle stealing techniques Burying men killed by Indians Killing an Apache (continued on reel 143)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview (Box 45, Folder 3, Reel 143)
    Bud Moore and Indian Killings, War between bandits Cattle stealing techniques Burying men killed by Indians Killing an Apache (continued from reel 142 on reel 144)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview, April 13, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 3, Reel 144)
    Bud Moore and Indian Killings, War between bandits Cattle stealing techniques Burying men killed by Indians Killing an Apache (continued from reel 143)
  - II: Brock, Henry Interview - story of Fred Murray (continued on reel 145), October 9, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 3, Reel 144)
  - I: Brock, Henry Interview - story of Fred Murray (continued on reel 144), II: Brock, Henry Interview; October 9, 1953; October 10, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 4, Reel 145)
    Bronco Bill Description of Pioneers Foundation (by Lou Blachy)
  - III: Brock, Henry - Interview, December 19, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 4, Reel 145)
    Kicking Geronimo in pants Killing of Miller Apache stealing horses Cowboys attacked by Apaches (continued on reel 146)
  - I: Brock, Henry - Interview, December 19, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 4, Reel 146)
    Kicking Geronimo in pants Killing of Miller Apache stealing horses Cowboys attacked by Apaches (continued from reel 145)
  - II: Brown, G. Cleve and Reatha Ellen-Interview, September 12, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 4, Reel 146)
    Thorn, Merle and Jenelyn - Interview Blachly, Lou Browns recollection of early days (continued on reel 147)
  - I: Brown, G. Cleve and Reatha Ellen-Interview, September 12, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 5, Reel 147)
    Thorn, Merle and Jenelyn - Interview Blachly, Lou Browns recollection of early days (continued from reel 146)
  - II: Bryan, Tom - Interview, June 26, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 5, Reel 147)
    Ft. Summer Recollections of Billy the Kid (continued on reel 1948)
  - I: Bryan, Tom - Interview, June 26, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 5, Reel 148)
    Ft. Summer Recollections of Billy the Kid (continued from reel 147)
  - II: Burgess, Ida - Interview (continued on reel 149), July 19, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 5, Reel 148)
  - I: Burgess, Ida - Interview (continued from reel 148), II: Burgess, Frank - Interview - recollection of early day (continued on reel 150); July 19, 1952; February 18, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 6, Reel 149)
  - I: Burgess, Frank - Interview - recollection of early day (continued from reel 149), February 18, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 6, Reel 150)
  - I: Burris L. Frank - Interview, October 25, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 7, 151)
    Billy the Kid not killed by Pat Garret Black Jack Ketchum was not hung Jesse James was not killed Ed Kelley killed Bob Ford (continued on reel 152)
  - I:Burris L. Frank - Interview, October 25, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 7, 152)
    Billy the Kid not killed by Pat Garret Black Jack Ketchum was not hung Jesse James was not killed Ed Kelley killed Bob Ford (continued from reel 151)
  - II: Church, Mrs. - Interviews, August 8, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 7, Reel 152)
    Killing of Sheriff Brady Harold War Store keeping in Lincoln Basis for McSweeny Feud (continued from reel 151 and on 153)
  - I: Church, Mrs. - Interviews, August 8, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 8, Reel 153)
    Killing of Sheriff Brady Harold War Coming to Lincoln in 1873(continued from reel 152 and on 1534)
  - I: Church, Mrs. - Interviews - Coming to Lincoln in 1873 (continued from reel 153), August 8, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 8, Reel 154)
  - I: Clapp, Mrs. Ellen Lucy - marriage, May 30, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 1, Reel 155)
  - II: Clark, undated (Box 46, Folder 1, Reel 155)
  - III: Cooper, Bill - Reminiscences of Duncan and Grant Co. (continued on reel 156), August 28, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 1, Reel 155)
  - I: Cooper, Bill - Reminiscences of Duncan and Grant Co. (continued from 155), II: Cowan, Millard - Billy the Kid; August 28, 1952; October 26, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 1, Reel 156)
  - I: Brock, Henry and Cox. John - Interviews, II: Cox, John T. - Interview - Collections of the West (continued on reel 158); April 11, 1953; July, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 2, Reel 157)
  - II: Cox, John T. - Interview - Collections of the West (continued on reel 157), II: Cox, John T. - Interview; July, 1952; June 7, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 2, Reel 158)
    Ambush of Black Jack, Killing of Bob Hayes Geo Musgrave shot Parker (continued on reel 1959)
  - I: Cox, John T. - Interview, June 7, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 3, Reel 159)
  - Cox, John T. - Interview - attempted jailbreak in Juarez (continued on reel 160), June 7, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 3, Reel 159)
  - I: Cox, John T. - Interview - attempted jailbreak in Juarez, June 7, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 3, Reel 160)
  - I: Culberson, Mrs. Victor - Interview (continued on reel 162), March 27, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 4, Reel 161)
  - I: Culberson, Mrs. Victor - Interview (continued from reel 161), II: Prestridge, Leta - Interview; III: Cunningham, Elton and Capitola Head - Interview - Life and early days of Mogollons (continued on reel 163); March 27, 1960; February 24, 1952; February 28, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 4, Reel 162)
  - I: Prestridge, Leta - Interview, II: Cunningham, Elton and Capitola Head - Interview (continued from reel 162 and on 164)); February 24, 1952; February 28, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 5, Reel 163)
  - I: Prestridge, Leta - Interview, II: Cunningham, Elton and Capitola Head - Interview (continued from reel 163); II: Cunningham, Elton - Interview; IV: Cunningham, Elton and Capitola Head - Interview; February 24, 1952; February 28, 1952; February 22, 1952; February 29, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 5, Reel 164)
    Pinno by mule-back to Mogollon Butch Cassidy and Pinkerton Detectives (continued on reel 165)
  - I: Cunningham, Elton - Interview, II: Cunningham, Elton and Capitola Head - Interview (; February 22, 1952; February 29, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 6, Reel 165)
    pinno by mule-back to Mogollon Butch Cassidy and Pinkerton Detectives (continued from reel 164)
  - III: Cunningham, E.A., 1952 (Box 46, Folder 6, Reel 165)
  - I: Cunningham, Elton - Interview, undated (Box 46, Folder 6, Reel 166)
    Reading of documents to show his life and story of Butch Cassidy Gang (continued on reel 1967)
  - I: Cunningham, Elton - Interview, undated (Box 46, Folder 7, Reel 167)
    Reading of documents to show his life and story of Butch Cassidy Gang (continued from reel 1966)
  - I: Darnell, Clinton E. and Lily Roberts (continued on reel 169), December 10, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 7, Reel 168)
  - I: Darnell, Clinton E. and Lily Roberts (continued on reel 169), December 10, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 8, Reel 169)
  - I: Dean, Reed - Interview, June 26, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 8, Reel 170)
    Marrigage, Killing of Davis Brac and Grostote
  - II: Stockbridge, Jack - Interview - Bear Moore, III: Wetherill, Marietta - Interview - Descent into Grad Gulch; IV: Stevens, Montaque - Interview - Concerning Suzie in cave; undated (Box 46, Folder 8, Reeler 170)
  - I: Dean, Reed - Interview - Reminiscences of Western New Mexico, August 10, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1, Reel 171)
  - I: Dean Reed - Interview, September 27, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1, Reel 172)
    Trail Drive to Wyoming Celebration in Denver
  - I: Dean Reed - Interview, September 27, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 2, Reel 173)
    Early days in Jacksburg Trail Driving to Pecos- return to Texas Covered Wagon E. Reserve, hunting lions Blizzard of 1888 Montague Stevens
  - I: Doolittle, Walter and Helen - Interview, May 3, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 2, Reel 174)
    Truth or Consequences, New Mexico Recollections of Caesar Brock
  - I: Dow, Bob and Allston, Seth - Interviews - Reminiscences of early days and story of life, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - I: Eckles, Miss Isabel Lancaster - Interview, >Johnson, Mrs. Mary Eckles - Interview; March 6, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 3, Reel 176)
    Santa Fe, New Mexico Coming of family School in Silver City Big Ditch Teaching School
  - I: Eckles, Bell - Interview - Chased by Villistas (school superintendent), undated (Box 47, Folder 4, Reel 177)
  - I: Fairlamb, Stella - Interview (Box 47, Folder 4, Reel 178)
    Thayer, Bertha - Interview Thayer, Kathleen - Interview Nutter, Evelyn - Interview Fairlamb, Ethel - Interview Recollections of Pioneer day (continued on reel 179)
  - I: Fairlamb, Stella - Interview (Box 47, Folder 5, Reel 179)
    Thayer, Bertha - Interview Thayer, Kathleen - Interview Nutter, Evelyn - Interview Fairlamb, Ethel - Interview Recollections of Pioneer day (continued from reel 179)
  - II: Ferris, Chester - Interview - Indians (Box 47, Folder 5, Reel 179)
  - Forsythe, Harvey - Interview (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Reminiscences of Father First Saturday in Apache War The first shovel in Santa Rita pit Growth of mining in Santa Rita
  - I:Fountain, Mrs. Terecita, April 7, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 6, Reel 181)
    Reminiscences of early days in Mex Mexico, riot in La Mesilla and killing of John Lemon
  - Fulton Col. Maurice - Interview, November 1, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 6, Reel 182)
    Colonel Fulton letters, Testimony Investigation of Tunistall murder (Testimony of Billy the Kid on killing Tusistall(
  - II:Fulton Col. Maurice - Interview, August 8, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 6, Reel 182)
    Developing an interest in Billy the Kid, Lincoln County War, Acquisition of Tunstall papers (continued on reel 183)
  - I:Fulton Col. Maurice - Interview, August 8, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 7, Reel 183)
    Developing an interest in Billy the Kid, Lincoln County War, Acquisition of Tunstall papers, Billy the Kid on the witness stand, Tunstall letter to Family in England (continued from 182>
  - II: Fulton, Col. Maurice reading Tunstall letters dated August 15, 1876, August 17, 1876, August 24, 1876, August 25, 1876 (continued on reel 184), September 24, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - I: Fulton, Col. Maurice reading Tunstall letters dated August 15, 1876, August 17, 1876, August 24, 1876, August 25, 1876(continued from reel 183, September 24, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 7, Reel 184)
  - II: Geer, Mrs. Taylor - Interview - Recollection of Murder A.T. Blachly (continued on reel 185), September 7, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 7, Reel 184)
  - I: Geer, Mrs. Taylor - Interview - Recollection of Murder A.T. Blachly (continued from reel 184), September 7, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 8, Reel 185)
  - I: Getts, Cora Henderson - Interview, September 8, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 8, Reel 187)
  - II: Cole, Frank Russell - Interview, undated (Box 47, Folder 8, Reel 187)
  - III: Stevens, Bill Joe - Interview, undated (Box 47, Folder 8, Reel 187)
  - IV: Laskowski, Vera - Interview, undated (Box 47, Folder 8, Reel 187)
  - V: Blachly, Lou - Recollections of Delta, Colorado, undated (Box 47, Folder 8, Reel 187)
  - I: Gipe, Amos Walter - Interview, July 6, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 1, Reel 188)
    Recollections of coming to New Mexico and of an 1893 robbery
  - I: Gordon, L.A. - Interview, July 19, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 1, Reel 189)
    Reminiscence of first autos in Mogollon Duck Creek in early days
  - I: Graham, Henry - Interview, July 7, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 2, Reel 190)
    Reminiscences (continued on reel 191)
  - I: Graham, Henry - Interview, July 7, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 2, Reel 191)
    Reminiscences of early days (continued from reel 190 and on 192)
  - I: Graham, Henry - Interview, July 7, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 3, Reel 192)
    Apache Creek, New Mexico (continued from reel 191)
  - II: Haralson, James Culbertson - Interview, July 26, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 3, Reel 192)
    Travel to Waco, Texas, Breaking up sod, What happened to Grandfather's 45 niggers after the war, Building a log cabin (continued on reel 1993)
  - I: Haralson, James Culbertson - Interview (continued from reel 192), July 26, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 3, Reel 193)
  - II: Haralson, James Culbertson - Interview, July 20, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 3, Reel 193)
    Building the Ft. Worth and Denver railroads. Getting caught in a Northern and seeing thousands of frozen antelope (continued on reel 194)
  - I: Haralson, James Culbertson - Interview, July 20, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 4, Reel 194)
    Building the Ft. Worth and Denver railroads (continued from reel 193)
  - II: Haralson, James Culbertson - Interview, July 20, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 4, Reel 194)
    Taking up new land. Well Drilling (continued on reel 195)
  - I: Haralson, James Culbertson - Interview, July 20, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 4, Reel 195)
    Taking up new land (continued from reel 194)
  - II: Harbottle, Mrs. Mary Ann rose (Mamo) - Interview, May 27, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 4, Reel 195)
    San Diego, California (continued on reel 196). Mother of Mrs. Jack Lewis
  - I: Harbottle, Mrs. Mamie - Interview (continued from reel 195), May 27, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 5, Reel 196)
  - I: Harrington, Tass - Interview, October 22, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 5, Reel 197)
  - I: Harrington, Tom and Tass - Interviews, October 23, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 6, Reel 198)
    Recollections of early days in Texas
  - Hauser, Russel - Interview, July 9, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 6, Reel 1999)
    Montrose, New Mexico?
  - I: Gray, Mary Olive - Interview, July 9, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 7, Reel 200)
    Recollections
  - II: Hennesy, George - Interview (continued on reel 201), undated (Box 48, Folder 7, Reel 200)
  - I: Hennesy, George - Interviews (continued from reel 200), undated (Box 48, Folder 7, Reel 201)
  - II: Holson, Charley W. - Interview (continued on reel 202), June 7, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 7, Reel 201)
  - I: Holson, Charley W.- Interview (continued from reel 201 on 203), June 7, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 8, Reel 202)
  - II: Holson, Charley W.- Interview (continued from reel 202 and on 204) (Box 48, Folder 8, Reel 203)
  - I: Holson, Charley W.- Interview (continued from reel 203 and on 205, June 7, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 1, 204)
  - < (Box 49, Folder 1, Reel 205)